Okay, now in this lecture, I'm going to show you a quick demo of inference optimization.
So I'll show you how you can use the cross region inference profile and latency optimization.
So before we go to the console, just want to show you
some butter three Python code that I have written.
So through which I'm going to access this Amazon Nova Pro model.
So here I have this bedrock invoke model, then I'm defining the model ID.
So rather than using Amazon Nova Pro, I'm seeing us dot Amazon dot Nova Pro,
which means I'm using cross region inference profile, but it's not global.
It's specified to the US geographic location.
Next, I'm just passing this prompt, what is Amazon bedrock and let me just go to the left.
Then I have some inference configuration parameters here, max token size, temperature, and so on.
And then if you just see here, I have added the guard rail identifier.
So remember, this is from one of the previous lectures,
where we had created the investment advice guard rail.
So I just took that guard rail ID value and put it here.
And then we had this version as draft.
And now let's look at this performance configuration latency.
So the value I had provided here is optimized.
In the previous lecture, we saw that there are two possible values optimized and standard.
So you can see here, standard and optimized.
Okay, now let me just copy this code and then I'll just go to the AWS console.
So I'm on AWS console.
So let me just open AWS lambda and here we have lambda.
So I'm in the US East one region, not Virginia.
So let me just click on create function.
And we have to give a name of the lambda function.
So I'll just give it a name demo inference optimization.
So we'll just select the latest one python 3.14 and then we'll just leave everything as it is.
Just click on create function.
Okay, we'll just make a couple of configuration changes.
So I'll just click on this configuration, click on edit.
Just let just increase the timeout.
So I'll just say one minute and then I'll just do save.
Now we have to give this lambda function permission so that it can access Amazon bedrock.
So I'll just click on this permission.
Let's just open this role in a new tab.
Okay, so this is our I am role.
So I'll just click on add permission, attach policies.
So let's just give it an admin access for now.
And let me just click on add permission.
So this is not what it should do in the production environment.
But for this demo purpose, I think it's okay.
So I'll just go back to the lambda function.
So I'm here on the lambda function.
Let me click on code.
Okay, so we have some boilerplate code.
So let me just paste the code had copied.
And let me just click on this deploy.
Okay, it's showing successfully deployed the function.
And you can see we already have the prompt here hard coded what is Amazon bedrock.
Okay, now let me just go ahead and click on test and create new test event.
Let me just say test 01 and then I'll just do a save.
Okay, now let me just close this and let me test again.
So we can see it generated some output.
Okay, so it generated the output if I just pull it up.
So you can see here it generated the body.
And then if I just go to the functional logs here.
So if we just go to the functional logs here, these are the functional logs.
So you can see it's providing some details around the request ID and date.
There it's saying context length and some other parameters.
But we'll just look at this performance configuration latency.
And you can see it is optimized, which we had provided as part of a request.
And it will also show you the invocation latency.
So three, one, one, three. So if we had not provided this parameter optimized,
maybe it would have been more. Okay, so that's pretty much it from this lecture.
So I have shown you two things how you can optimize performance latency.
And the second thing I have shown you here is how you can use the cross region inferencing.
And you can see here we have this us.amazon.nova.
So this is case of geographic cross region inferencing.
And if you wanted global, you could have put global instead of the us.
Okay, so that's pretty much it from this lecture.
I'll see in the next lecture. Thank you.